晚上好啊阿婆们 姑娘之夜在外小聚啊
Evening, ladies. Gals' night out?
吃着派 聊着帅哥 真欢乐啊
Chasing guys, eating pie,having fun.
这桌子粘乎乎的 快那破抹布擦擦吧
This table is sticky!Run a damp rag across it!
把这收拾干净能死啊
Would it kill you to clean a little?
你们这到底是啥地方啊
What kinda place is this?
这里的汤都是冷的
The kind that serves soup cold.
还有 你那夸张的耳环是咋回事儿
And what's with your crazy earrings?
难不成你是吉普赛人
What are you, some kinda gypsy?
喔 淡定啊 阿婆们
Whoa! Hold up, ladies.
人老不是犯贱的理由啊
You don't get a bitch pass just 'cause you're old.
对 你们没听错 我就是说了
Yes, that's right.I said it.
你们进来吃饭 还一副黑社会老大的态度
You come in here with your gangster granny attitude,
想把怒火都发泄在
think you can get away
我这个吉卜赛服务员身上
with dumping all over the lowly gypsy waitress.
没门 在我们餐厅 没歧视你们老已经不错了
No way. At this diner, we don't discriminate due to age.
如果你么非这么混蛋下去
If you're gonna act like an ass,
我也要像对待混蛋一样对待你们
I'm gonna treat you like an ass...
等会你们的屁股摔得多痛可不管我事了 （ass的两个意思 大家自己体会 此处意译）
No matter how close that ass is riding to the floor.
好了 现在我再把桌子擦一下 然后我们从头开始
Now, I'll wipe off the table we'll take it from the top.
嗨 我是服务员Max 你们想来点木薯粉吗
Hi, I'm Max. Who wants tapioca?
这才像样嘛
That's more like it.
把你们的不爽都发泄到孙子孙女身上吧
Save the disappointment for the grandkids.
Earl 我需要另一本支票本
Earl, I need another book of checks.
刚才的一本掉在冰箱和烤箱的夹缝里了
The last one fell between the refrigerator and the oven.
当我正要去拿的时候我被夹在
I'd reach for it,but that falls between
“我不想拿”和“擦 我才不拿”的矛盾里了
"I don't do that"and "Oh, hell no."
Max 快看那边 穿西装的男女
Look overthere, Max.Men and women in suits.
我们的社区真是蒸蒸日上啊
This neighborhood is definitely on the rise.
我还记得我看到一个黑人
I remember a time when a black man
不能叫出租车
couldn't get a cab around here.
那件事就发生在这周三
And that time was Wednesday.
Max 我刚和2号桌那对聪明的夫妇聊天了
Max, I was just talking to the smart couples in booth two.
他们是第一个在这里把croque monsieur
I know they're smart because they're the first people in here
正确发音的人
who ever ordered the croque monsieur
他们一定是聪明人
as croque monsieur and not "crock monster."
他们想见见做蛋糕的人
They wanna meet the woman who made the cupcakes.
我跟他们说你马上就过去
I told them you'd be right over.
-去吧 他们多好啊 -不 他们一点也不好
- Go! They're so nice.- No, they're not nice.
他们是时髦的吸血虫
They're trendy, blood-sucking locusts
专门到这个社区里来掠夺 摧毁一切
who come into this neighborhood to pillage and destroy
我所关心的东西
everything I care about.
深有同感
I felt the same way when the Hilton sisters
当年希尔顿姐妹就是这么毁了我的21岁生日
crashed my 21st birthday.
啥事儿
What?
这些蛋糕是你做的吗
You made these cupcakes?
是的 有啥问题 快说吧 姐忙着呢
Yeah, what's the problem? Spit it out, I've got a life.
我们就是想告诉你 你的蛋糕实在是
We just wanted to tell you that your flavor palate is...
太好吃了
amazing.
我不知道你是谁 也不知道你从哪里来
I don't know who you are or where you came from--
我自己都不清楚
Neither do I.
但是这些蛋糕真是完美
But these are fabulous.
欢迎你们来我们社区哈
Well, welcome to the neighborhood.
我就知道我喜欢你们
I knew I liked you guys.
那些吸血中想干啥
So what did the trendy locusts want?
你太爱瞎点评了 你知道吗
You are so judgmental, you know that?
他们告诉我 我的蛋糕太完美了
They wanted to tell me the cupcakes are "fabulous."
谢谢
Thank you.
也许从现在开始你终于可以适应
Maybe now you'll finally start to get it
除我以外的人告诉你这些蛋糕有多美味
if someone besides me tells you how good they are.
我想那个形容词一定是“完美”
I believe the word was "fabulous."
Max 端菜
Pick up, Max.
Oleg 以后你要叫我会做完美蛋糕的
Oleg, from now on, you may call me Countess Max
Max女爵
of the Fabulous Cupcakes.
你以后要叫我Oleg先生
And you may call me Sir Oleg
因为我的裤子里也有好东西哦（大家自行体会）
of the Amazing Party in My Pants.
Caroline 那些快乐的西装男女
Caroline, the happy,shiny people in suits
让我把这张小纸条给你
asked me to give you this note.
啊 太好了
Oh, what a great idea!
他们建议我们到他们大厦楼下的咖啡店里
They suggested we sell Max's cupcakes
销售Max的蛋糕
at the cool new coffee place in their building.
可是你们已经在我的餐厅卖蛋糕了啊
But you already sell cupcakes here in my diner.
Han 我们的蛋糕是一项事业
Han, we're building a cupcake business that will one day
总有一天我们会离开这里的
get us out of here.
这就是我们人生的奋斗目标
That's what we're trying to do with our lives.
但我本以为我们有些特殊的关系呢
But I thought we had something special.
是 但那不是我们人生中的唯一
Yes, but we're not exclusive.
这间餐厅很可爱 但我想要获得更多
The diner's cute, but I want more than this.
嗷
Oof.
就像被初恋女友又甩了一次
First girlfriend all over again.
+
嗨 Johnny
Hey, Johnny.
Max照料墙那边的生意
Max has the tables against the wall.
我们坐在你这边就行了
Oh, we're good in your section.
Caroline 见见我的好兄弟Carlos吧
Caroline, I want you to meet my buddy Carlos.
Hi.
嗨
我去柜台忙了
Well, I'm working the counter.
你怎么了老兄 给点力啊
What's happenin'? Come on, dude.
你可是纽约大学文学专业的高材生啊
You have a literature degree from NYU.
我不想承认 但是当我紧张的时候
I didn't mean to say that, but when I get nervous,
我的家乡口音就显露出来了
my Rico Suave comes out.
我保证绝对不会再发生
It won't happen again.
菜单给你们
And here's two menus.
杂~样~啊~亲~
What's happenin'?
拜托 我真的很紧张
Dude, I'm nervous.
各位 我负责那一片桌子
Hey, guys, I'm in that section over there.
我们坐在Caroline这片也挺好的
Oh, we're good in Caroline's area.
如果你不怕热咖啡洒裤裆上
Well, if you like hot coffee in your pants area,
you're in the right place.
就放心大胆的坐这儿吧
其实 我挺喜欢那样的
Actually, I like that.
等好吧
Coming right at you.
Johnny坐在你那片儿
Johnny's in your section.
是啊 为什么
Yeah, why?
他每天晚上就是为了见你而来的
He comes in here every night to see you.
他是你的朋友 也是你的暗恋对象 还可能是随便什么东西
He's your friends or...crush or whatever he is.
他才不是我的暗恋对象呢 他只是
Shh! He's not a crush. He's a...
我不知道他是啥 但无论怎样
I don't know what he is, but whatever he is,
他今天坐在你那片了
he's in your section.
- Max - 噢 你怎么来了
- Max! - Ooh! What are you doing?
你不能进来的
You're not supposed to be in here.
我知道 谁让我是个坏男孩呢
I know, I'm a bad boy.
听着 今天我没有坐在你那一片
Look, the reason I'm not sitting in your section
是因为我朋友Carlos特别喜欢Caroline
is because my buddy Carlos is crushing pretty hard on Caroline
他让我去给他俩牵线
and he asked me to do what I can to hook them up.
噢 所以现在你既是个管吧台的
Oh. So now you're a bartender,
还是个街头艺术家 更是个拉皮条的
a street artist, and a pimp.
Ain't nuttin' wrong with me
pimpin' some boy on the side.
Keeps me in spray paint and whatnot.
So?
From pimp to pimp...
帮忙跟Caroline说说吧
Help me out with your girl.
我的姑娘才不会这么廉价呢
My girl don't come cheap.
这里面还真热啊
[Nervous giggle] Is it hot in here?
是啊 而且咱们还是在一个冰库里
Yes, and we're in a freezer.
这是我的冰库
Yes. My freezer.
呃 我就是想和Max说几句话
I was, uh, just talking to Max.
外面见
Um, I'll see you out there.
这就是你喜欢的男人类型吗
So is this what you like in the men?
才不是呢 他只是个有耍流氓的顾客
No. He's just a customer that went rogue.
他看起来又弱又娘
He is weak and girlish.
像你这样的女人 需要一个真汉子的陪伴
A woman like you needs a real man.
常言道啊
You know what they say.
只要你去过一趟乌克兰 你就会知道爱爱也是会很痛的 （大家意会吧……翻不出来）
Once you go Ukraine, you will scream with sex pain.
把这句“常言”翻译成英语 还真让人提不起性致
That probably lost some of its sensual appeal
不过还是谢谢你的提议
in the translation, but thanks for the offer, Oleg.
他很可爱，但不是我喜欢的型
Cute, but I'm not interested.Besides, he's not my type.
你就直说吧
Just say it.
你对他不感兴趣 因为他是波多黎各人
You're not interested in him because he's Puerto Rican.
你怎么会这么想
Where did you get this idea
谁说我只和白人约会啊
that I would only date white guys?
提醒一下你 我可是和很多种男人约会过的
For your information, I'vedated all kinds of men.
我曾经在蒙特卡洛和一个西班牙人约会过
I once had a Spaniard in Monte Carlo.
那不是ABBA组合的一首歌么
Isn't the title of an Abba song?
你真的不想和他约会吗 他挺可爱的
Are you sure about this? He's cute.
看遍了白人帅哥 也来一点异国风情尝尝鲜嘛
And trust me, you could use a little salsa in your white rice.
Max 我刚刚变得一贫如洗
Max, I just lost every dollar I had.
我现在对男人没想法
The last thing on my mind right now is guys--
无论什么类型的男人
any type of guy.
除了这个小帅哥
Except this guy.
嗨 小栗子
Hi, Chestnut.
我现在更专注于我们的事业
I'm much more concerned with our business
and getting my head back above water.
男人早晚都会有的
Men will come sooner or later.
根据我的研究 男人总是“来”的很快
Well, according to my research most men come sooner.
我觉得我们明天应该到那家咖啡店去
Oh, I thought we should stop by
向他们毛遂自荐
that new coffee place tomorrow and introduce ourselves
还有推荐我们的蛋糕
and your cupcakes.
我才不要就这样走进去 我感觉我在“卖”自己
I'm not gonna walk in there.I feel like I'm selling out.
我们得改改“卖”这个词
Okay, let's reframe the phrase selling out
应该是“卖出”
and make it sold out,
比如 Max 我们把蛋糕全卖出去了
as in "Max, we sold out of the cupcakes"
我们终于成功了
and are now successful."
What's that you say?
I can now afford to buy the wax dental floss again?
Fine.
我这么做就是为了让你先把我们的事业忘掉一会
But I'm only doing it so you'll eventually get your mind
然后找个男人欢乐一把
off the business and get laid.
你怎么就觉得我这么需要爱爱呢
Why do you think I need to get laid so badly?
如果我也和你一样
If I'd just gone through all the tension and trauma
经历这么多的创伤
that just happened to you,
I'd be climbing telephone polls to take the edge off.
我都愿意“爬”电线杆来减压
信我一句吧 我现在想的最少的就是爱爱
Trust me, sex is the last thing on my mind right now.
还有 说到改变
Oh, and speaking of reframing things,
我给你准备了个惊喜
I have a surprise.
我把我的屋子重新装饰了一翻
I redecorated my room.
I scoped out some cheap fabric in bedding places
我在Houston 大街的布匹店里
down on Houston Street.
仔细的选购了这些廉价布料
What do you think?
看看怎么样
I think you've made a vagina.
我觉得你把床整成了阴道形
What?
啥
Sister, you may think that sex is the last thing
姐们 也许你觉得爱爱是你最不关心的事
但是你把你的床装饰的像个阴道
on your mind, but you turned your bed into a vagina.
难道你觉得我的阴道还有帘子吗
Do you think my vagina has curtains?
我可不知道那有多“长”（邪恶的Max 啊……）
I don't know how long it's been.
我累坏了 我要去睡了
I'm tired. I'm going to bed.
去吧  我还要做一些蛋糕
Okay, but I still have to make the cupcakes
明天好拿到咖啡店去
to bring by that place tomorrow.
我不想打扰你
I don't wanna keep you awake
要不你就睡我屋里的床吧
so why don't you sleep in my bed tonight
然后我今晚睡你的床
and I'll pass out on your vagina?
好 但明早你可得给我买早餐
Okay, but you better buy me breakfast in the morning.
我喜欢这儿 就像20年代的巴黎
I love this place. Looks like Paris in the '20s.
这些人更像一帮20多岁装模作样的年轻人
More like poseurs in their 20s.
呦 这地方还真被打扫过
Man, they've really cleaned this place up.
你以前来过这儿吗
You've been here before?
来过 这以前是卖酒的
Yeah, it used to be a liquor store
老板是个爱尔兰老男人
owned by this old Irish guy
他的老二上都有老年斑了
who had freckles on his penis.
有时候他把你逼到角落 然后露出来给你看
Sometimes he'd corner you and flash it,
但随后他都会给你一杯免费拿铁做补偿
but then he'd always comp you a free lotto ticket.
好 请你一定不要
Okay, well, let's try and keep
在我们销售的过程中
that sort of charming nostalgia
把那些“美好”往事给抖露出来
out of our sales pitch.
看 店主
Oh, that's the owner.
我仔细的观察过她了
I scoped it out before you got here.
记住 所有话都由我来说
And remember, I'll do the talking.
为啥我就不能开口呢
Why don't I get to talk?
说雀斑老二吗
Freckled penis.
还有 我经验比你丰富
And besides, I have more experience.
所有作为PEE俱乐部的成员
All those who pitched business models to Warren Buffett
在巴菲特那工作过的
as a member of the Phillips Exeter Entrepreneurs Club
和姐击掌庆祝下
raise their hands. Holla!
好吧 如果这件事儿真的值得击掌庆贺
Well, if you care enough to raise your arms about it,
还是你来说吧 我什么都不说
fine. You talk. I won't say anything.
嗨 想要什么
Hi, what can I get for you?
嗨 我是Caroline 这是我的合作伙伴Max
Hi, I'm Caroline and this is my business partner Max.
- 你的名字是 - semhar
- And you are? - Semhar.
- 我的神啊 - 多好听的名字啊
- Oh, jeez.
- Such a pretty name.
在梵文中 它是老虎之光的意思
It means "light of the tiger" in Sanskrit.
我了个去
Oh, jeez.
是我的瑜伽名字
It's my yoga name.
谁救救我吧
Help me, God.
Semhar 我们刚刚开始一项蛋糕事业
Well, Semhar, we just opened
是一家本地公司
a local neighborhood cupcake company.
这是我们的卡片
Our card.
我们正在向附近的面包店
We're introducing our exciting product
介绍我们的产品
to local boulangeries.
请尝一下吧 Max快拿过来
Please try a sample. Max.
你是想要椰奶咖啡味的还是巧克力咖喱味的
Would you like coconut-coffee, chocolate-curry,
或者是蓝莓柠檬味的
or blueberry-lemon zest?
我最爱吃椰奶咖啡味的
My absolute fave is the coconut-coffee.
尝尝这个吧 好吗
Let's start with that, shall we?
谢谢 不过还是不必了
Thank you, but no thank you.
我们可以知道为什么吗
Well, can I ask you why?
它们不够好看
They're not pretty enough.
拜托 你说啥
Excuse me?
他们真的不够好看
They're not pretty enough.
也许你尝一尝
Perhaps if you tried one,
你就会知道这些蛋糕有多美味
you'd see how amazing our flavor palate is.
Hold off, Flava Flav.
你说他们不好看是什么意思
What do you mean,they're not pretty enough?
他们看起来就像家庭烘烤出来的一样可爱
They have a charming homemade look,
但是这里的消费者想要
but my customer would prefer
更好看 更上档次的产品
a more upscale, prettier product.
友情提示 你这家上档次的咖啡店
Just FYI, some upscale residents
所在的这栋上档次的大厦
in this very upscale building
有一些上档次的居民最近告诉我们
where your upscale store actually is located
他们觉得这些蛋糕太完美了
recently told us they were fabulous.
我明白
I understand.
但他们实在是不够漂亮
But they're not pretty enough.
听着
Listen, battlefield earth.
这里是纽约的布鲁克林
This is Williamsburg, Brooklyn,
没有什么东西能改变一个事实
and no amount of exposed brick and paint
就在你所站的地方
can change the fact that,right where you're standing,
我看见Tommy o'hanlon老二的次数
I've seen Tommy O'Hanlon's wing-wang
多的我自己都记不清
more times than I care to remember.
而且我必须说 你的态度比他的老二还要冒犯我
And I must say, it was way less offensive than your attitude.
你把你那上档次的头发也剃了吧
And you can shove that up your upscale.
我们走
Let's go.
合十礼
- Namaste.- Namaste.
+
Max 这里怎么空了
What's with the empty hands, Max?
今晚没有蛋糕吗
No cupcakes tonight?
没有 蛋糕让我很不爽 我今晚不打算做了
No, they're bugging me. I decided to take the night off.
小心这样的决定啊
Be careful with decisions like that.
In 1987, I took a night off
from earth, wind, and fire
and the next day, they
earth, wind, and fired my ass.
抱歉 我来晚了
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
在你的阴道床里小憩了一会儿吗
Mid-afternoon nap in your vagina?
我倒想
I wish! No.
我去了Greenpoint的一家廉价烘烤用品商店
I went to a cheap bakery supply store in Greenpoint
给我们买了写东西
and got us some supplies.
看
Here.
这是一个基础蛋糕装饰工具
It's the basic cake decorating kit.
我还给我们找了件好事
And best of all I found us a fun,
两节蛋糕装饰课
reasonable two-session cupcake decorating class
在一家面包房
at a bakery.
我们可以学着做漂亮的小玫瑰花了
We can learn how to make pretty roses.
没门
No way.
蛋糕根本不需要那么漂亮
The cupcakes don't need to be pretty.
幽默感就可以弥补了
They compensate by having a great sense of humor.
好看的蛋糕只是我们的另一种选择
Pretty cupcakes is just another option for our business.
人们喜欢漂亮的 我们就做漂亮的
People want pretty, we do pretty.
人们喜欢家常的 我们就
Or people want homemade, we do--
-等等 我们的家常自制蛋糕呢 -今晚我们做
- Wait, where is our homemade?
- I didn't make any tonight.
你一个也没做吗
You didn't make any?
你就因为别人的一点批评
What, you get one piece of constructive criticism
就不打算做蛋糕了吗
and you stop making them?
Max 这是我们的事业
Max, it's business.
而且关于把蛋糕做漂亮 也许Semhar说的有点道理
And maybe Semhar has a point about making them pretty.
首先 她知道啥是漂亮吗
First of all, what does she know about pretty?
那女人的长发辫吓死人了
The woman has dreadlocks.
她的头就像
Her head looks like the stuff
从吸尘器里倒出来的垃圾似的
you empty out of a vacuum cleaner bag.
一点也不漂亮
Not pretty.
忘了她吧
Forget her.
你怎么了
What's happening with you?
你对变漂亮有意见么
What's your problem with pretty?
别做出那个歌唱家的手势
Don't wave your
divas live hand at me.
我就是觉得我们这个社会
I just think society's way too concerned
太在乎别人想的漂亮了
with other people's idea of what's pretty.
你是觉得自己做不好
You don't think you can do it.
这才是事情的原因
That's what this is about.
并不是因为这个社会
This isn't about society.
你害怕你不能把蛋糕做漂亮
You're afraid you can't do pretty.
听着 我就是不想做的漂亮
Look, I don't do pretty
就像你不愿意和波多黎各人约会一样
the way you don't do Puerto Ricans.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我愿意“做”他
I'll do Puerto Ricans.
那好吧
All right.
去做一个 让我一个人待一会儿
Then go do one and leave me alone.
Max 这只是一项技能 就这样
Max, it's a skill. That's all.
不知道怎么做一件事 并不可耻
It's not shameful to not know how to do something.
难道你没有从小开始学钢琴的经历吗
Didn't you have piano lessons growing up?
你开玩笑呢吧
Seriously?
滑冰呢
Ice skating?
我最接近滑冰的一次
Closest I've come to blades on ice
有个怀孕的女孩想拿刀捅我
was when a pregnant girl pulled a knife on me
在一场曲棍球比赛里
at a hockey game.
听着 我们现在有一项事业
Look, you and I have a business,
把蛋糕做漂亮就是一项我们需要的技能
and this is a skill we need.
我们一定要去上课
We're going to that class
然后成为把蛋糕做好看的大师
and we are gonna master how to make pretty roses.
我知道你讨厌一切时髦的东西
And I know how much you hate anything trendy,
所以我找到了布鲁克林一家意大利家庭面包店
so I found us a family-owned Italian bakery in Brooklyn.
意大利人可好了
Italian's good.
也许在我把你杀了以后
Maybe they'll know how to dump the body
他们知道怎么埋尸体
after I kill you.
首先 欢迎各位来到美美味蛋糕店
First of all, welcome to Spice and Sugar.
我们在做面包时有一个小小的变化
We did a little twist on the traditional sugar and spice
先放香料进去
putting spice first because...
因为我们是意大利人~
Both: We're Italian.
我们总是先把香料放在最上
And we always got the spice up front
再把一些放在最下
and a little in the rear.
给力哦~
Both: Holla!
想到你以前也说过“给力” 你是不是觉得很尴尬啊
Now are you embarrassed you ever said holla?
我名字叫Stephanie 这是我的表妹serena
My name is Stephanie, and this is my cousin Serena,
我们家族经营这家面包店很多年了
and this bakery has been in our family for years
现在我们接手了这家面包店
and then we took it over and made it...
把它变得更火辣了~
Both: Hot.
好好好 让我们先各自做一下自我介绍
All right, let's go around and introduce ourselves
并告诉我们来这里的原因
and tell us why you came tonight.
先从这个帅小伙开始吧
Let's start with the cute guys.
必须的！
Both: always!
我叫steve 我要办一个单身派对
I'm Steve, I thought this would be
做蛋糕会是一个好想法
a fun idea for my bachelor party.
我就要和michale结婚了 就是这位
I'm getting married to Michael...right there.
真可爱 上帝保佑你
So cute. God bless!
我是michale
And I'm Michael.
我也叫michale 我也叫michale
- I'm Michael as well.
- Michael.
哇 好多michale
Oh...So many Michaels.
你呢 我也叫michale
- And you are?
- Michael.
不 我叫max
No, I'm Max.
她真有趣 好可爱 上帝保佑你
Oh, she's funny. So cute, God bless!
我是Caroline 我是Max的搭档
And I'm Caroline. I'm Max's partner.
好多基佬拉拉在这里啊 我就知道
- Oh, so many gays tonight.
- I know.
不不 我是她的商业合作伙伴
No, I'm her business partner.
我们在Williamsburg有自己的蛋糕事业
We actually have our own cupcake business over in Williamsburg,
我必须说 我们做的还不错
and I must say, we're doing very well.
Max是烘焙师 我负责销售
Max is the baker and I'm the business head
今晚我们想提升业务技术
and we're here tonight to increase our skill level
把我们的事业提升到一个新高度
and take our business up to a level that's...
和你们这儿一样火辣~
Hot as well.
如果你要说这么多话
If you're gonna talk that much,
我们就没时间学习了
no one will have time to learn anything.
我就知道
I know, right?
你们的面包店在哪里啊
So, uh, where's your shop?
现在我们只是在自己的公寓里做蛋糕
Well, right now, we're just working out of our apartment.
那么说就是没有店咯 还真可爱
- So no shop.
- Oh, that's sweet.
真好玩  祝你们好运 上帝保佑你
- Cute.
- Yeah, good luck, God bless.
你是不是嫉妒了
Can you say jealous?
好 我们从最简单的开始学
All right, let's start simple
做简单的冰花
with a pretty little icing flower.
每个人拿好奶油滚边带
Everybody pick up your piping bags,
注意要用直的一边
and with a straight-edge tip--
你们基佬可以用弯的
But you guys can use your gay-edge tip.
好 每个人跟着学
All right, everybody watch Stephanie.
把这个固定住
You're gonna take the nail head
然后做出个U形
and you're gonna make a little "U"
小花瓣就出来了
so that you get little petals.
重复五次就行了
And we'll do this five times.
然后一朵漂亮的五瓣花就诞生了
And then, you have a pretty little five-petal flower.
真简单  多可爱 太有趣了
- Simple.
- So cute. How fun!
不不 要做成U字型
No, no. You gotta start by making a "U".
这就是U啊
I did. That's a "U".
serena 这是U吗  不 这不是
- Serena, is that a "U"?
- Not a "U".
行 我重新做
Fine, I'll start over.
那明明是U
That was a "U".
难道就因为我没有实体店
And what, just because I don't have a quote-unquote shop
我就不知道U是啥了么
I don't know a "U"?
什么态度啊
What's with the attitude?
得 咱么走吧
All right, let's leave.
等这些基佬再笑的时候 我们就溜出去
Next time the gays giggle, we'll just slide out.
不 我们是来学习的
No, we're here to learn.
这看起来不错
That looks good.
我烂透了 我要崇左
I suck. I'm starting over.
Max 你为什么要这样 那明明很好
Max, why'd you do that? It was good.
还不够好啊
Not good enough.
你们还没做好吗
You two not done yet?
你必须学会做小花
You have to master the little flower,
否则等到学做玫瑰花的时候你就是一团糟了
or when we move on to roses you'll be screwed.
你说呢  绝对是一团糟
- Right, cuz?
- Oh, totally screwed.
实在是很糟糕
Screwed and not in the good way.
你觉得我们该不该告诉他们
Do you think we can convince them
互相扇耳光是一种新的庆贺方式
that slapping each other's face is the new high five?
steve 天啊 这小花太美了
Steve, oh, my God. That rose is gorgeous.
你真棒
Good for you.
好了 还有一分钟 然后就要展示玫瑰了
All right, one more minute and we'll display our roses.
嗨 steve 帮个小忙吧
Psst. Steve. Little help.
考试一计时我就完蛋 我SAT考试才得40分
I choke at timed tests. I got like a 40 on my SATs.
我擦类 steve
Damn it, Steve!
看看这儿
Look at this place.
在这种经济环境下
There's no way these girls
女孩子做蛋糕事业根本不可能成功
could have this much cupcake success in this economy.
我说 这栋楼的开支得多大啊
I mean, the overhead on this building alone--
你说啥呢
What are you saying?
又不是在说钱
Not saying mob money,
只是说也许我们也能开家店
just saying maybe we'd have a shop too
只要我们有一大笔钱   嘘嘘
- if we had mob money.
- Shh.
小点声儿
Keep it down.
你想明天醒来一早
You wanna wake up tomorrow with Chestnut's head
就看到小栗子的头在你的阴道床上吗
in your vagina bed?
时间到了 看看你们做的怎么样
Okay, time's up. Let's see what you got.
那是个啥 我怎么感觉啥也没有
What is that? There's like nothing there.
那不是玫瑰花
That's not a rose.
那是个迷你艺术品  随便吧
- It's minimalist.
- Whatev.
不是随便吧 这个可厉害了
No, not "whatev". It's brilliant.
当我在东京的时候
And I would know because,when I was in Tokyo,
我上了几节私人日式插花课
I had a private Japanese flower arranging class
是插花研究所的专家教的
with the head of the Ikebana institute.
他还说我有天赋呢
And he said I had a gift.
用他的话说 （日语)
In his words,
"Caroline...[Speaking Japanese]"
随便吧 你的朋友做的怎么样
Whatev. Okay, what about your friend there?
我时间不够了
I kinda ran out of time.
你有20分钟呢
[Scoffs] You had 20 minutes.
她说你可是个烘培师啊
I thought she said you were the baker.
你应该20秒就做好
No, you need to be able to whip these out in like 20 seconds
如果你想把那家小面包店做成功
if you wanna be successful in your little bakery.
我想要个蛋糕 12个小时候来取吧
"Um, I'd like a cupcake."
"That'll be 12 hours."
是不是 就是
- Right?
- Right.
而且要做的比这个还好看
And they have to be prettier than that.
也许明天你会做的更好
Well, maybe you'll do better tomorrow.
记得你们的家庭作业
Remember. Your homework assignment
做一个有漂亮的玫瑰花的蛋糕
is to bring in a cupcake with a pretty rose on it.
好
[Scoffs] Right.
说的跟我们还会再来似的
Like we're gonna come back here
还和这些罗伯特德尼罗混在一起
and spend time with these Robert de Nir-hos.
啊 又毁了一个 我擦
Ugh! That one stinks too. Damn it!
[Clatter]
Max 先放一会儿吧
Max, forget it.
三点了 快去睡觉
It's 3:00 A.M. Go to bed.
别跟我说话
Don't. Don't say anything to me.
我正在生你的气呢
I am so mad at you right now.
为什么  为你做的所有事
- What did I do? - Everything.
我以前最喜欢做蛋糕了
I used to love making cupcakes.
我只有在做蛋糕的时候
It was the one thing I could zone out and do
才不用动脑子
without thinking.
现在我尽在动脑子了
And now all I'm doing is thinking.
想着我蛋糕做的有多烂
Thinking that I stink at making cupcakes.
别想了
Well, stop it.
谁关心他们的想法 她们只是蛋糕恶霸
Who cares what they think? They're bitchy baking bullies.
我们不用再回去了
We don't have to go back there.
然后呢
Oh, and then what?
我会觉得我做的蛋糕不够好
I'm gonna think my cupcakes weren't good enough
余生在郁闷中度过
for the rest of my life?
既然你说我们需要这项技术 我们就要掌握这项技术
You said we need the skill,then we need the skill.
我虽然有很多坏毛病 但绝对不是半途而废的人
I'm a lot of things, but I'm not a quitter.
我要做一个傻不拉唧的漂亮蛋糕出来 哪怕得把自己活活折腾死
I'm gonna make a stupid,pretty cupcake if it kills me.
或者你
Or you.
你也要和我一起去
And you are going back there with me.
我们要把我们的漂亮蛋糕
And we're gonna shove our pretty cupcake
好好让snooki和她表妹开开眼 （此处是关于泽西海滩的笑话）
right up Snooki and her cousin's asses.
现在闭嘴 别跟我说话
Now, shut up, don't talk to me,
回你的阴道床睡觉去
and go back in your vagina.
很抱歉让你看到这些了 小栗子
Sorry you had to see that, Chestnut.
+
嗷 不怎么好看
Oh, not very pretty.
不过至少你已经尽力了michale
But at least you tried, Michael.
还有一个问题
Just one question.
你确定你是基佬吗
Are you sure that you're gay?
好 caroline 看看你做的
Oh, okay, Caroline. Let's see your pretty rose.
我没做
I didn't do one.
这个社会太关注别人的想法了
Society is way too concerned with other people's idea
关于什么是美丽
of what's pretty.
随便吧
Both: Whatevs.
好 你的烘培师做了么
Okay, what about your baker there?
她也没做吗
She bail too?
不 她做了
No, here it is.
哇 Max 这真好看
- Mm-hmm.  - Max, that's so pretty.
真是以你为荣啊
I'm so proud of you.
做的真好 上帝保佑你 你太棒了
Good work, God bless. Good for you.
你做了多久
How long did it take you?
3小时40分钟
About three hours and 40 minutes.
但是我成功了
But I did it!
我只是想向你们和自己证明
I just wanted to prove to you and myself
我能把东西做的很好看
I can make something pretty.
现在我就……
And now that I have--
啊
Mm!
[All shout, gasp]
那种蛋糕不是我的风格 我不做徒有外表的东西
That cupcake wasn't me. I don't do pretty.
但是我还做了一些蛋糕
But I did make each of you a cupcake that I think says
可以表达我对这个蛋糕课程的看法
what I feel about this whole cupcake class.
这个写着 去死吧
This one says "Bite me".
这个写着 滚你丫
This one says "Screw U".
看见没 这才是U
You see that "U"? That's a "U".
给力吧
Holla!
好吧 祝你好运
Well, good luck with that.
人们可不喜欢这些冒犯他们的蛋糕
People don't want cupcakes that insult them.
天啊 Max 这就是我们该做的
Oh, my God, Max. That's our thing.
我错了 你是对的
I was wrong. You were right.
我们不需要做好看的蛋糕
We don't need to make pretty cupcakes.
别的人都做好看的蛋糕
Everybody does pretty.
我们要做你最擅长的
We have to do what you do best.
吐槽别人
Insult people.
是啊 可是谁会买呢
Yeah, who's gonna buy that?
我们会 为我们的洗礼会
We will. For our shower.
And really let us bitches have it!
制作 UB 感谢收看 实在不了解的地方没有翻译
更好的翻译还请期待伊甸园 风软 破烂熊